<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>English on</title><link>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/tags/English/</link><description>Recent content in English on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/tags/English/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Genre</title><link>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Genre/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Genre/</guid><description>Genre Genre&amp;rsquo;s are ways of writing and speaking that help people interact, communicate, and work together They help writers with strategies and guides to focus their ideas They help readers know what to expect Genre&amp;rsquo;s are flexible They are adaptable to various situations They can be played with, not inherently strict or required to be followed They evolve to suit various fields They shape [[Rhetorical Situation]]&amp;rsquo;s and readers interpretations List of Genre&amp;rsquo;s [[Rhetorical Analysis]]</description></item><item><title>Library Research</title><link>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Library-Research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Library-Research/</guid><description>Library Research Home | Purdue Libraries
lib.purdue.edu We have access to a LOT of databases They can all be accessed through the Purdue Library website Databases have collections of articles usually of a single discipline JSTOR and Academic Search Complete are good general ones You can use AND OR and NOT to change search results Always try to limit to linked full text and scholarly sources only Use authors last name when saving file, since that&amp;rsquo;s part of how you cite it Name files smartly so they&amp;rsquo;re easy to keep track of and fine later Tips &amp;amp; tricks for database searches Vary search terms, use synonyms Try multiple databases, not all have same articles Use AND OR NOT Limit searches to scholarly articles only</description></item><item><title>Prewriting</title><link>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Prewriting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Prewriting/</guid><description>The first stage of the [[Writing Process]] is just coming up with ideas, also known as prewriting Three main ways to come up with ideas are Prewriting - use of visual and textual/verbal strategies to just get ideas down on paper Heuristics - Time tested techniques that help you ask good questions to figure out what information you need to support your thesis or claim Exploratory writing - reflective strategies to help you understand the topic and how you feel about it Prewriting Concept mapping, clustering ideas together Free writing, just write as much as you can to get ideas going This is a part of the writing process, so if it&amp;rsquo;s done right then it will greatly help during [[Drafting]] and [[Revising]] Any plan is better than no plan.</description></item><item><title>Rhetoric</title><link>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Rhetoric/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Rhetoric/</guid><description>Rhetoric rhetoric is often associated with persuasion more broadly though, rhetoric is a collection of tools and techniques at our disposal for crafting effective messages &amp;ldquo;messages&amp;rdquo; refers to almost any kind of writing or speech eg writing, narrating, presenting, arguing etc.</description></item><item><title>Rhetorical Analysis</title><link>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Rhetorical-Analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Rhetorical-Analysis/</guid><description>Rhetorical Analysis A [[Genre]] used for analyzing a (usually) scholarly article rhetorically.
Rhetorical Analysis is a way to interpret a text to determine why it is or is not effective Usually focuses on an authors [[Rhetoric|rhetorical]] decisions e.</description></item><item><title>Rhetorical Situation</title><link>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Rhetorical-Situation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Rhetorical-Situation/</guid><description>Rhetorical Situation The rhetorical situation is a specific set of [[Rhetoric|rhetorical]] devices that make up a text Topic - What am I writing about?</description></item><item><title>Writing Process</title><link>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Writing-Process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://monsterico.github.io/ObsidianNotes/Writing-Process/</guid><description>Writing Process The writing process goes [[Prewriting]] -&amp;gt; [[Drafting]] -&amp;gt; [[Revising]] -&amp;gt; [[Reflecting]]</description></item></channel></rss>